https://www.cru.org/sg/en/about/privacy.html

About
Would You Like to Know God Personally?
Understand how you can know God personally.
What is Christianity?
Everything you wanted to know about the Christian faith.
FAQ
Get the answers to frequently asked questions on Christian beliefs and practices.
Dealing with Life's Questions
Explore answers to life's biggest questions.
My Story: How My Life Changed
We all have a story. Read about individuals who have been transformed by faith.
A New Reason to Live
Our Daily Lives Are Shaped By Our Beliefs.
What Is The Next Step You Want To Take On Your Spiritual Journey?
Courses & Events
A collection of courses and events organised by Cru Singapore.
The Significance Project
A discipleship course that incorporates life-coaching methods along with facilitators and personal peer coaches in order to help you to discover your personal mission.
FamilyLife
FamilyLife provides transferrable, biblically-based help for you at every stage of your marriage and family life.
ThriveSg
ThriveSg is a ministry that seeks to empower people to thrive significantly by promoting emotional wellness & resilience, through cultivating self-discovery, providing emotional healing and supporting personal growth.
Spiritual Growth
Take the next step in your faith journey with devotionals, resources and core truths.
Life & Relationships
Explore life's questions from trials and hardships to dating and marriage.
Bible Studies
Find resources for personal or group Bible study.
Share the Gospel
Understand evangelism and strategies to help share your faith story.
Help Others Grow
Help others in their faith journey through discipleship and mentoring.
Digital Ministry
At Cru, we've seen firsthand how digital tools can be used for advancing the Great Commission. Digital allows access to places and people that have never been reachable before, and we want you to be a part of reaching people with the gospel.
thriving-in-transition
Athletes
Engaging around sports to help athletes think and live biblically.
Campus
Helping students know Jesus, grow in their faith and go to the world to tell others.
Families
Equipping families with practical approaches to parenting and marriage.
Musicians & Artists
Bringing the unchanging Gospel to a changing generation.
Professionals
Connecting in community for the well-being of the city.
Careers
Consider how your passion, gifts and vision might align with ours so that we might partner together to reach the world...
Volunteer
Would you like to give your time to work with Cru? We need you.
Missions
Imagine a trip that could change cities, countries and continents around the globe while also forever transforming your life - Missions with Cru will do just that.
From the National Director
Spiritual Growth
Life & Relationships
Sharing the Gospel
Helping Others Grow
LiveSg Stories
How To Give
Here you can find out how to give financially through various ways.
Information for Donors
Our commitment to donors, and a list of FAQs.
Statement of Faith
What we believe about the gospel and our call to serve every nation.
Our Leadership
Our History
Cru Singapore's milestones through the years.
Our Values
Leading from values so others will walk passionately with God to grow and bear fruit.
Contact Us
Subscribe to our Mailing List
About
Statement of Faith
Our Leadership
Our History
Our Values
Contact Us
Subscribe to our Mailing List
Search
Knowing God
Would You Like to Know God Personally?
What is Christianity?
FAQ
Dealing with Life's Questions
My Story: How My Life Changed
A New Reason to Live
Train & Grow
Courses & Events
The Significance Project
FamilyLife
Personal Data Protection
As part of its charitable activities, Cru Asia Ltd (CAL) and its divisions Cru Singapore and East Asia School of Theology (EAST) collect personal data from its donors and stakeholders for administration, fundraising, media sales, events seminars, education programmes and corporate communication purposes. The Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (PDPA) establishes a data protection law that comprises various rules governing the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal data.
CAL has adopted a corporate policy for personal data protection in line with PDPA requirements. PDPA recognises both the rights of individuals to protect their personal data, including rights of access and correction, and the needs of organisations to collect, use or disclose personal data for legitimate and reasonable purposes.
Collection of Data
CAL may collect personal data on its website or in various application and response forms. Personal data are collected during fundraising activities, media and book sales, mission trips, ministry events, seminars, programmes and from those who attend classes at EAST.
Communication and Use of Data
The Board recognises the importance of donor and stakeholder confidentiality and requires the executive leaders to closely adhere to the Singapore statutes and guidelines given by the Personal Data Protection Commission.
Our stakeholders may be contacted periodically on activities, programmes, courses, events, media sales, ministry opportunities or benefits available through CAL and its divisions. We may disclose personal data to third-party vendors and adjunct lecturers who may assist us with events, seminars, courses, mission trips, programmes and corporate communications.
Media
As we are a community-based organisation, we often share photos or videos of CAL activities over our newsletter, website and social media channels. If you attend a CAL activity, your image may be taken in photos or videos of the event which may be retained and published by CAL. collect the following types of personal information:
Donors
CAL is committed to financial integrity, donor confidentiality and accountability. CAL will ensure that donors receive accurate and ethical information about the organisation, and the intended use, value and tax implications of donations. CAL and its divisions follow the fundraising guidelines practices set by the Singapore Commissioner of Charities and will ensure that its fund raising activities are transparent and ethical. CAL and its divisions may wish to acknowledge your donation and if you wish to remain anonymous, you may inform us in a note when you make the donation.
Donors may visit the Singapore Charities Portal at www.charities.gov.sg to search for current fundraising permits that were issued to “Cru Asia Limited”.
Contact Us
You may contact us to withdraw your consent and address any queries relating to the collection, use and disclosure of personal data to the Data Protection Officer at corpcomms@cru.org.sg or call us at +65 6589 9600.
Version 1.0
Published: 5/22/18 | 3:25pm EDT
Comments
Load Comments
©1994-2020 Cru. All Rights Reserved.
